Guide to the Yale University Master of Fine Arts Theses in Photography
Yale University Arts Library
- MFA Theses
  - [Untitled], 2004; Paige, Myles; 18 prints, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 214)
  - [Untitled], 2004; Partin, Theodore; 20 prints, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 215)
  - [Untitled], 2004; Reed, Jesse Finley; 29 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 216)
    Keywords: still lifes, close-up views, interior views
  - [Untitled], 2004; Wardel, Milan; 12 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 217)
  - [Untitled], 2005; English, Sara; 11 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 219)
  - [Untitled], 2005; Goranson, Andrea; 14 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 9.25 x 12 inches (Box 220)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), still lifes
  - Not My Chalet, 2005; Kanai, Anna; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11.25 x 17 inches (Box 221)
    Master copy DVD located in Box 174. Use copy DVD located in Box 175. Videos are titled: "snowdrift," "merrily down the stream," "northern snow," "the entire length of a warehouse," "forest," "forest II," and "toxic eden."
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), architecture (object genre), nature photography
  - [Untitled], 2005; LaMar, Connelly Blake; 35 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 7 x 9.5 inches (Box 218)
    Keywords: documentary photography, portraits, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2005; Lehr, John; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 222)
  - [Untitled], 2005; Lepore, Anthony; 14 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 223)
    Keywords: religions (concept), family, domestic animals, portraits, landscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2005; Mahoney, Brian; 10 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 224)
    Keywords: manipulated photographs, still lifes, motion photographs
  - [Untitled], 2005; Potter, Kristine; 13 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 13 x 16 inches (Box 225)
  - [Untitled], 2005; Vosacek, Jennifer; 1 DVD, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; video art (Box 174)
    Master copy DVD located in Box 174. Use copy DVD located in Box 175.
  - [Untitled], 2006; Albaugh, Lisa; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 229)
    Keywords: interior views, still lifes, landscapes (representations), portraits
  - Visible Cities, 2006; Baumgartner, Marisa; 24 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 13 x 19 inches (Box 230)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), cityscapes (representations), photomosaics (photographs), digital imaging
  - [Untitled], 2006; Cahill, Tommi; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 231)
  - [Untitled], 2006; Doty, Craig; 12 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 232)
    Keywords: interior views, portraits, fantasy
  - [Untitled], 2006; Drumgoole, Jennifer; 7 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 2 personal photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 226)
    Master copy DVD located in Box 174. Use copy DVD located in Box 175. Videos are titled, "HUSKY" and "Wing Bowl 13."
  - [Untitled], 2006; Gordon, Daniel; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 2 personal photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 227)
    Keywords: digital imaging, photomosaics (photographs), still lifes
  - Highly Decorated, 2006; Montgomery, Colin; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 228)
    Keywords: portraits, landscapes (representations), interior views, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2006; Sexton, Allison; 11 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 book of photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 233)
    Keywords: portraits, townscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2006; Young, Spencer; 22 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 234)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), interior views, still-lifes
  - [Untitled], 2007; Abeles, Michele; 13 prints, 1 artist statement; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 235)
  - [Untitled], 2007; Almanas, Kathryn Parker; 25 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 list of works; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 236)
    Keywords: medical centers, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2007; Bangsted, Thomas; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 list of works; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 10.75 x 20.5 inches to 16 x 19 inches (Box 237)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), nature photography, close-up views
  - [Untitled], 2007; Deevakul, Pete; 16 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 personal photograph; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 15 x 19 inches to 16 x 20 inches (Box 238)
    Master copy DVD located in Box 174. Use copy DVD located in Box 175. Video is titled, "Fianchetto."
    Keywords: interior views, still lifes, portraits
  - [Untitled], 2007; Johnson, Leigh; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 list of works; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 16 x 20 inches to 20 x 24 inches (Box 243)
  - [Untitled], 2007; Lefrak, Ashley; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 list of works; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 13.5 x 13.5 inches to 13.5 x 16.5 inches (Box 239)
  - [Untitled], 2007; Reisinger, Reka; 14 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 list of works, 1 personal photograph; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 240)
  - [Untitled], 2007; Sherry, David Benjamin; 14 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 list of works; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 8.25 x 16.25 inches to 16 x 20 inches (Box 241)
    Keywords: manipulated photographs, photomosaics (photographs), portraits, nudes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2007; Soderholm, Rebecca; 6 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 list of works, 1 book of photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box 242)
    Master copy DVD located in Box 174. Use copy DVD located in Box 175. Video is titled, "White Wedding."
    Keywords: portraits, nature photography
  - [Untitled], 2008; Contis, Samantha Hallie; 27 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 19 x 24 inches (Box 246)
  - [Untitled], 2008; Davis, Jennifer Elizabeth; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 247)
  - [Untitled], 2008; Graf, Bryan Kenneth; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 book of photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 8.5 x 11 inches to 16 x 20 inches (Box 248)
    Keywords: manipulated photographs, landscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2008; Mosse, Richard Bartholomew; 34 prints, 1 submission form, 1 list of works; color photographs; Measurements:; 13 x 19 inches (Box 249)
  - [Untitled], 2008; Peters, Bradley Louis; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11.5 x 14.5 inches (Box 250)
  - [Untitled], 2008; Rudensky, Alexandra; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 251)
  - [Untitled], 2008; Stolfa, Sarah Rebecca; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 252)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), portraits, interior views
  - [Untitled], 2008; White, Marley Anne; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 253)
    Keywords: interior views, still lifes, portraits, landscapes (representations)
  - Homecoming: The Beauty of Absurdity, 2008; Yun, Suyeon; 28 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 13 x 19 inches (Box 254)
    Keywords: portraits, families, interior views, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2009; Awde, George Halim; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 255)
    Keywords: documentary photography, portraits, Lebanon
  - [Untitled], 2009; Donovan, Dru; 22 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 256)
    Keywords: portraits, figures (representations)
  - History of a Village, 2009; La Spina, David James; 48 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 personal photograph; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 4 x 5.5 inches to 22 x 30 inches (Box 257)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), portraits, interior views, architecture (object genre), townscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2009; Leonard, Justin Thomas; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 book of photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 7 x 10 inches to 8 x 10 inches (Box 258)
    Keywords: portraits, documentary photography, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2009; Maloney, Catharine Frances; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box 259)
    Keywords: portraits, men (male humans), figures (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2009; Price, Caitlin Teal; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 260)
  - [Untitled], 2009; Smith, Colin Patrick; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 13 x 15 inches to 13 x 18 inches (Box 261)
  - [Untitled], 2009; Stocki, Elaine; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 11 x 15 inches to 16 x 16.5 inches (Box 262)
  - [Untitled], 2009; Tse, Ka-Man; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 10 x 14 inches to 11 x 14 inches (Box 263)
  - [Untitled], 2010; Bush, David Martin; 24 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 264)
  - Between Mines and Mountains, 2010; Foglia, Lucas Forest; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 book of photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 265)
  - [Untitled], 2010; Greene, Kate Elizabeth; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 266)
    Keywords: nature photography, landscapes (representations), still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2010; Grigorenko, Tatiana; 26 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 2 miscellaneous documents; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 9.5 x 14.5 inches to 13.5 x 20 inches (Box 267)
    Master copy DVD located in Box 174. Videos are titled, "Family Galaxy" and "News at Five."
    Keywords: manipulated photographs, portraits, landscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2010; Hatleberg, Curran Patrick; 26 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 21 inches (Box 268)
    Keywords: portraits, documentary photography, urban areas
  - [Untitled], 2010; Hooper, Tiffani Sharlene; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 15 x 20 inches (Box 269)
    Keywords: figures (representations), portraits, interior views
  - [Untitled], 2010; Mulligan, Rory P.; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 16 x 20 inches to 20 x 24 inches (Box 270)
    Keywords: portraits, nudes (representations), landscapes (representations), men (male humans)
  - Home Theater, 2010; Slovenc, Hrvoje; 11 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 8.75 x 18.5 inches to 8.75 x30 inches (Box 271)
    Keywords: photomosaics (photographs), interior views
  - [Untitled], 2010; Szilada, Monika; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 272)
    Keywords: photomosaics (photographs), portraits, documentary photography
  - [Untitled], 2011; Abu-Shaheen, Manal; 33 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 273)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), portraits, cityscapes (representations), documentary photography
  - [Untitled], 2011; Barnett, Gideon; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 22 inches (Box 274)
    Keywords: museums (buildings), close-up views, portraits
  - [Untitled], 2011; Booth, Matthew; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 275)
    Keywords: still lifes, interior views, manipulated photographs, digital imaging, fantasy
  - [Untitled], 2011; Grubb, Matthew; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 personal note, 1 personal photograph; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 276)
  - [Untitled], 2011; Hart, Heyward; 16 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 277)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), cityscapes (representations), portraits
  - [Untitled], 2011; Hely-Hutchinson, Victoria; 17 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 278)
    Keywords: portraits, interior views, architecture (object genre)
  - [Untitled], 2011; Park, Soyoung; 32 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 279)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), portraits, cityscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2011; Prinos, Georgios; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 280)
  - [Untitled], 2011; Uibopuu, Terttu; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 281)
  - Sweet Home, 2012; Baker, Peter J.; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 14 x 20 inches (Box 114)
    Keywords: portraits, urban areas, industrial districts
  - [Untitled], 2012; Choi, Richard; 9 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 282)
    Keywords: families, portraits, still lifes, close-up views, interior views
  - [Untitled], 2012; Gardiner, Thomas Edward; 23 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 15.5 x 20 inches to 17 x 20.5 inches (Box 283)
    Keywords: portraits, urban areas, rural areas
  - Desire, 2012; Her, Pao Houa; 22 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 11 x 7 inches to 11 x 9 inches (Box 284)
    Keywords: portraits, nudes (representations), still lifes, families, men (male humans), women (female humans)
  - Chosen Blood, 2012; Koti, Katie R.; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 9 inches (Box 285)
    Keywords: portraits, nudes (representations), landscapes (representations), models (representations), rural areas, families
  - [Untitled], 2012; Merrill, Kate A. T.; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 13 x 16.5 inches to 13 x 18 inches (Box 286)
    Keywords: portraits, nudes (representations), landscapes (representations), domestic animals, families, Maine, rural areas
  - Forest Hills, 2012; Muehlbauer, Sarah R.; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 17 x 22 inches (Box 287)
    Keywords: exterior views, interior views, still lifes, portraits
  - [Untitled], 2012; Rodriguez Cid, Felix; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 16 inches (Box 288)
    Keywords: portraits, manipulated photographs, fantasy, urban areas
  - [Untitled], 2012; Strauss, Maayan; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 9 inches (Box 289)
    Keywords: models (representations), rural areas, portraits, interior views, still lifes, families
  - [Untiltled], 2013; Abrahamik, Marzena; 21; color photographs; Measurements:; 19 x 13 inches (Box 290)
  - [Untitled], 2013; Beal, Endia Sherie; 8; color photographs; Measurements:; 12 x 15.25 inches, 12 x 17.5 inches (Box 291)
  - [Untitled], 2013; Bick, Elizabeth Rose; 19; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 16 x 13 inches to 19 x 12.5 inches (Box 292)
  - [Untitled], 2013; Case-Hofmeister, Johanna Ruth; 18; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches, 7.5 x 10 inches (Box 293)
  - [Untitled], 2013; Kha, Tommy; 19; color photographs; Measurements:; 13 x 17 inches (Box 294)
  - [Untitled], 2013; Marcelle, Michael Barry; 1 (Box 295)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Only use copies of magnetic or digital media may be viewed.
  - [Untitled], 2013; Ruspoli di Poggio Suasa, Sophie; 37; black-and-white photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 21 x 16 inches, 17 x 11.5 inches, 25 x 17 inches (Box 296)
  - [Untitled], 2013; Schmitz, Justin Phillip; 1 (Box 295)
  - [Untitled], 2013; Wechsler, Sadie Marie; 26; color photographs; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 6 inches to 13.5 x 10.5 inches (Box 297)
  - [Untitled], 2013; Yribe, Rick George; 18; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10.5 inches (Box 298)
  - [Untitled], 2014; Desmond, Erin; 19; Measurements:; 11 1/8 x 14 1/4 inches (Box 299)
  - [Untitled], 2014; Erizku, Awol; 20 photographs, 1 box slip; Measurements:; 10.25 x 12.5 inches (Box 300)
  - High Yellow, 2014; Gaignard, Genevieve Ruth; 2 photography magazines, 1 submission form, 1 artist statement; Measurements:; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box 301)
  - [Untitled], 2014; Hummel, Hannah Flora; 13; Measurements:; 10.5 x 14 inches (Box 302)
  - [Untitled], 2014; Ishino, Fumikazu; 20; Measurements:; 5 x 7 inches (Box 303)
  - [Untitled], 2014; McGonagle, Casey Robert; 18 photographs, 1 USB flash drive; Measurements:; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box 304)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes a USB flash drive in the guise of a voodoo doll; drive contents include a music folder and a video folder.
  - [Untitled], 2014; Moore, Tyler Zachary; 23; Measurements:; 8.5 x 11 inches, 12 x 10.5 inches (Box 305)
  - [Untitled], 2014; Price, Hannah; 13 photographs, 1 pair of white gloves; Measurements:; 22 x 26 inches (Box 306)
  - [Untitled], 2014; Stultz, Melissa Erin; 23; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 307)
  - [Untitled], 2014; Whale, Evan; 20; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 308)
  - Rough Draft, 2015; Alekhuogie, David Osawindawen; 1; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 resume (Box 309)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Arctander, Zakary D.; 20; 1 submission form, 1 miscellaneous document (Box 310)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Gorbutt, Quinn; 19; 1 submission form, 1 personal note, 1 miscellaneous document (2 pages) (Box 311)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Magowan, Isabel; 18; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 flash drive (4GB) (Box 312)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Meyohas, Sarah; 19; 1 submission form, 2 miscellaneous documents ("Stock Performance," "Bitch Coin") (Box 313)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Perez, Elena; 23; 1 submission form (Box 314)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Rand, Bryson Dowell; 34; 1 submission form, 5 miscellaneous documents (Box 315)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Soffa, David Mellor; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 poem (Box 316)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Szwarc, Ilona Anna; 19; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 317)
  - [Untitled], 2015; Thornton, Anne Chapman (Box 318)
  - Not Nice Pictures, 2016; Atherton, Ray, 1883-1960; Atherton, Monique; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 319)
  - [Untitled], 2016; Brown, Drew; 25; 1 submission form, 1 poem (Box 320)
  - [Untitled], 2016; Cwynar, Sara; 16; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 flash drive (Box 321)
  - [Untitled], 2016; Durst, John Eli; 22; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 322)
  - [Untitled], 2016; Edmonds, John; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 323)
  - [Untitled], 2016; Kelley, Cole; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 324)
  - [Untitled], 2016; Kim, Ye Weon Mary; 33; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 325)
  - [Untitled], 2016; Myers, Robin; 17; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 326)
  - [Untitled], 2016; O'Leary, Eva; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 327)
  - [Untitled], 2016; Pape, Adam; 35; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 328)
  - [Untitled], 2017; Al Qasimi, Farah; 21; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 329)
  - [Untitled], 2017; Brewer, Lance; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 331)
  - [Untitled], 2017; Griffin, Harry John, III (Box 332)
  - [Untitled], 2017; Leifheit, Matthew; 18; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 book of photographs, 3 magazines, 2 newspapers (Box 333)
  - [Untitled], 2017; Olesen, Walker; 34; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 334)
  - [Untitled], 2017; Res; 26; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 335)
  - [Untitled], 2017; Shimshak, Anna; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 336)
  - If It Rained an Ocean, 2017; Singer, Danna; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 337)
  - [Untitled], 2017; Tran, Chau; 21; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 338)
  - [Untitled], 2018; Bowman, Dannielle; 15; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 339)
  - death to the photo patriarchy, 2018; Calivas, Jennifer Helene; 10; 1 submission form,1 flash drive (Box 340)
  - [Untitled], 2018; Chan, Penn; 34; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 341)
  - death to the photo patriarchy, 2018; Freyer, Jillian; 15; 1 submission form (Box 342)
  - Blue-Stained Walls, 2018; Harrison, Kathryn; 20; 1 artist statement, 1 submission statement (Box 343)
  - death to the photo patriarchy, 2018; Lennon, Lacey; 14; 1 submission form (Box 344)
  - [Untitled], 2018; Moore, Lucus; 15; 1 artist statement, 1 submission form (Box 345)
  - death to the photo patriarchy, 2018; Pustka, Evelyn Louise; 15; 1 submission form, 1 artist statement, 1 flash drive (Box 346)
  - [Untitled], 2018; Swindel, Daniel; 19; 1 submission form, 1 flash drive (Box 347)